hikisaita yami ga hoe furueru teito ni
In the imperial capital, teared apart by the darkness,
ai no uta takaraka ni odorideru senshi-tachi
Singing high the song of love, the warriors come forth
kokoro made kōtetsu ni busō-suru otome
Girls, armed with the hearts of steel
aku o kechirashite seigi o shimesu no da
Fighting demons, and standing for justice
hashire kōsoku no teikoku kagekidan
Fast as light, Imperial Assault Force
unare shōgeki no teikoku kagekidan
Impactful as chant, Imperial Assault Force
hashire kōsoku no teikoku kagekidan
Fast as light, Imperial Assault Force
unare shōgeki no teikoku kagekidan
Impactful as chant, Imperial Assault Force
Ueno! Ueno!
Asakusa
Chapter 1
Imperial Assault Force—Flower Division
Imperial Navy ensign, Mr. Ōgami Ichirō
You're hereby appointed as a commanding officer of
"Imperial Assault Force, Demon Interception Unit, Flower Division"
In addition, you'll bear another, secret mission.
To join the unit, you're to head out to the Ueno Park.
Imperial Army Launtenant General, Maeda Ikki